{"question":"Mobile Shaders are ____ than Standard Shaders.","answer":"Lighter","option1":"Heavier","option2":"Darker","option3":"Faster","questionType":"Beginner"}
{"question":"Blend trees are used for :","answer":"Blend two or more animations.","option1":"blend two or more binary tree nodes","option2":"Convert 2d animations to 3d.","option3":"Enable root motion for animations","questionType":"Medium"}
{"question":"Vector3 Lerp(Vector3 a, Vector3 b, float x); where x is:","answer":"interpolation Value","option1":"Interpolation Angle","option2":"Interpolation Constant","option3":"Time Difference","questionType":"Beginner"}
{"question":"Which of them is true about Vector Normalisation?","answer":"Normalization makes the vector unit length.","option1":"Vector's value is set to zero and only direction is used.","option2":"Vector values are rounded to nearest values.","option3":"Vector direction is set to zero.","questionType":"Beginner"}
{"question":"What is the output of this line : transform.position.x=10;","answer":"ERROR; You cannot directly assign a value.","option1":"The GameObject moves to (1,0,0).","option2":"The position values of GameObject's Y,Z remain same but X is set to 1.","option3":"ERROR; You cannot assign a integer for a vector3 value.","questionType":"Beginner"}
{"question":"How do you rotate a GameObject using physics :","answer":"AddTorque()","option1":"Rigidbody.rotate()","option2":"transform.rotate()","option3":"Rigidbody.AddForce(force,angle)","questionType":"Beginner"}
{"question":"The purpose of isKinematic is : ","answer":"to make the body not get affected by other GameObject's physics.","option1":"to make an object immovable.","option2":"to turn off the object's gravity.","option3":"to disable collisions so that physics will not be calculated.","questionType":"Beginner"}
{"question":"Which of them is true for a static variable :","answer":"Only one instance exists.","option1":"Can only be set in the beginning of the program.","option2":"Can be used by other classes but value cannot be changed.","option3":"instances only exist in inherited classes. ","questionType":"Beginner"}
{"question":"Can you inherit from multiple classes in C#?","answer":"No","option1":"Yes","option2":"No, Can inherit multiple abstract classes","option3":"Yes, Can be done via multiple abstract classes and multiple interfaces.","questionType":"Beginner"}
{"question":"Can you inherit from multiple classes in C#?","answer":"No","option1":"Yes","option2":"No, Can inherit multiple abstract classes","option3":"Yes, Can be done via multiple abstract classes and multiple interfaces.","questionType":"Medium"}
{"question":"Which of them is wrong about constructors","answer":"a special type of methods\/functions.","option1":"Used to initialize a value.","option2":"can have zero or more constructors.","option3":"the compiler will add a constructor automatically if we don't write one.","questionType":"Beginner"}
{"question":"User defined constructors cannot have zero arguments :","answer":"No, User defined constructors can have any number of arguments.","option1":"Yes, User defined constructors must have atleast one argument as the compiler already provides a zero argument constructor.","option2":"We have to use the keyword override to use a zero argument constructor","option3":"We have to use the keyword virtual to use a zero argument constructor","questionType":"Beginner"}
{"question":"Can we use a public keyword inside the update() method?","answer":"No","option1":"No, we can use private keyword variables though.","option2":"Yes","option3":"local variables are always protected by default.","questionType":"Beginner"}
{"question":"What is the output : int i=0; Debug.Log(\"i++\");","answer":"i++","option1":"0","option2":"1","option3":"0 , 1","questionType":"Beginner"}
{"question":"What is the correct order of execution ?","answer":"Awake, OnEnable, Start ,Update, LateUpdate","option1":"Awake, Start, OnEnable ,Update, LateUpdate","option2":"Start, Awake, OnEnable ,Update, LateUpdate","option3":"OnEnable, Awake, Start , Update, LateUpdate","questionType":"Beginner"}
{"question":"Which of the following statements are true  :","answer":"Invokes cannot be paused","option1":"Coroutines are same as Invoke","option2":"Coroutines cannot be paused. ","option3":"Invokes and coroutines can take multiple arguments\/parameters.","questionType":"Beginner"}
